



Giacomo Ziveri

Date of birth: 06/03/2002 | **Nationality:** Italian | **Phone number:**

(+39) 3738589339 (Mobile) | **Email address:** ggziveri@gmail.com | **Website:**

https://gzifalsi.github.io/ | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/giacomo-ziveri/ |

Address: Via Carlo Valvassori Peroni 61, 20133, Milano, Italy (Home)

ABOUT ME

Technology expert with specialised skills in both hardware and software, with a particular focus on Linux systems. Mine has focused on the design, implementation and maintenance of IT solutions. I possess extensive experience in project management, a distinctive ability to configure and optimise systems, and a passion for continuously learning the latest technologies.

WORK EXPERIENCE

15/11/2021 - 23/01/2022 Milano, Italy

OMNICHANNEL EMPLOYEE ADIDAS

Responsible for driving sales and revenue growth across multiple sales channels including online, retail shops and wholesale accounts. In-depth knowledge of the adidas brand, excellent communication skills and a proven track record of driving sales in a fast-paced, dynamic environment.

13/02/2023 - CURRENT Milano, Italy

ICT CONSULTANT ALTEN

- AXWAY-based API infrastructure management, including configuration, monitoring and troubleshooting
- Keeping the API gateway up-to-date with the latest patches and security updates
- API testing with Postman
- Ticket management and onboarding of third-party companies on the API infrastructure
- Real-time analysis of logged data via Splunk

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

10/09/2016 - 10/06/2021 Milano, Italy

DIPLOMA DI MATURITÀ SCIENTIFICA IIS J.C. Maxwell

Website https://www.maxwell.edu.it/ | Final grade 85/100 | Level in EQF EQF level 4

10/09/2023 - CURRENT Milano, Italy

LAUREA IN INFORMATICA Università degli Studi di Milano

Website https://www.unimi.it/it | Field of study Computer use | Level in EQF EQF level 5

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ITALIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
INGLESE	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

Python | C/C++ | HTML/CSS/JS | Linux | Windows | Docker | Kubernetes | Splunk | Go | Git | REST APIs | MySQL | Ansible (Base) | Postman | Microsoft Excel | Server Linux Administrator | Axway API Management | PC Hardware Expert | Linux LPI-101 | Jira